ILGWU Audio-Visual (AV) 5780 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Would You Let Someone Do This To Your Sister? (Box 84, Folder 2)
  Video Cassette
- The Women of Summer & The Global Assembly Line (Box 84, Folder 3)
  short version; Video Cassette
- The Cooke Foundation for Special Education Presentation (Box 84, Folder 4)
  5:00; New York, NY; Video Cassette
- On The Job. Workplace Literacy & WLS News Story (Box 84, Folder 5)
  Secretary of State Literacy Office, Illinois State Library; R.T. 16:40 and 3:54; Video Cassette
- Ellis Island. Medals of Honor, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  WPIX Channel 11; July 3; Video Cassette
- Silent Danger (Box 84, Folder 7)
  English; Video Cassette
- Chinatown Manpower Project Workplace Literacy Program (Box 84, Folder 8)
  Garment-Related Bilingual TV Broadcast Lessons; Episode 9-15; Video Cassette
- Across the River with Hedrick Smith (Box 84, Folder 9)
  Hedrick Smith Productions, Bethesda, MD: Video Cassette
- UNITE Convention Highlights, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- The Truth Behind The Labels (Box 84, Folder 11)
  Fechheimer Uniforms; Video Cassettte; 2c
- Chinatown Manpower Project Workplace Literacy Program (Box 84, Folder 12)
  Garment-Related Bilingual TV Broadcast Lesson; Episode 1-8; Video Cassette
- Sewing Our Future. We Do The Work (Box 84, Folder 13)
  16:00; Video Cassette
- IGLWU It's About Jobs (Box 84, Folder 14)
  Video Cassette; 2c
- Zoned for Slavery. The Child Behind the Label, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  Video Cassette; New York, NY; National Labor Committee
- Joining Hands. New Members Video (Box 84, Folder 16)
  Local 23-25 ILGWU; English Version; 9:06; Video Cassette; New York, NY
- ILGWU Health Care. Gus Tyler/Bill Moyers Interview, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  March 18; With End Title; :30; Paula Green Adv.; Video Cassette
- ILGWU Chorus. IGLWU Convention, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  Hollywood, FL; June; Video Cassette
- Medals of Honor Awards Gala, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  Ellis Island; May 16; 68:00; Video Cassette
- Sharing What Works. Introduction to the Series, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  10:00; Center for Applied Linguistics & The Media Group, Washington D.C.; Video Cassette
- Off Center. An Audio Update for Labor Leaders, 1993 (Box 305, Folder 1)
  Audio Cassette; Winter; George Meany Center for Labor Studies
- Off Center. George Meany Center's Audio Magazine, 1991 (Box 304, Folder 1)
  Property of ACTWU Education Dept.; George Meany Center for Labor Studies; Audio Cassette
- The Music of American Politics. Joe Glazer (Box 303, Folder 1)
  Audio Cassette
- The Triangle Fire. As Told By Leon Stein (Box 302, Folder 1)
  Audio Cassette; Taped from Shorter Original tape
- Sweet Life. It's All That We Deserve (Box 297, Folder 1)
  Audio Cassette; Support the ITGLWF's Campaign Against Child Labour
- New York City Labor Chorus, 1993 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  Martin Luther King Jr. High School; June 19, 8 PM; Live; Audio Cassette
- IGLWU Anthem. Solidarity Forever. Look for the Union Label. Which Side are You On. Hold the Fort. Thousands with One Heart. We Shall Not Be Moved (Box 291, Folder 1)
  Audio cassette; ILGWU Chinese Chorus/Conductor & Soloist Ka-Kam Chui
- Unknown Audio Cassette (Box 306, Folder 1)
- Bayard Rustin. The Singer (Box 292, Folder 1)
  Audio cassette; 4c
- Joe Glazer Sings Labor Songs (Box 298, Folder 1)
  Audio cassette; 4c; Collector Records
- We Are One, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 31)
  VHS; Local 23-25 Chinatown strike
- F04 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 85)
  - F04 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 85, Folder 1)
- F04 -Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 86)
  - F04 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 86, Folder 1)
- F05 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 87)
  - F05 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 87, Folder 1)
- F05 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 88)
  - F05 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 88, Folder 1)
- F06 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 89)
  - F06 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 89, Folder 1)
- F06 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 90)
  - F06 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 90, Folder 1)
- F07 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 91)
  - F07 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 91, Folder 1)
- F07 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 92)
  - F07 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 92, Folder 1)
- F08 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 93)
  - F08 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 93, Folder 1)
- F08 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 94)
  - F08 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 94, Folder 1)
- F09 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 95)
  - F09 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 95, Folder 1)
- F09 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 96)
  - F09 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 96, Folder 1)
- F10 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 97)
  - F10 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 97, Folder 1)
- F10 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 98)
  - F10 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 98, Folder 1)
- F11 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 99)
  - F11 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 99, Folder 1)
- F11 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 100)
  - F11 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 100, Folder 1)
- F12 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 101)
  - F12 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 101, Folder 1)
- F12 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 102)
  - F12 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 102, Folder 1)
- F13 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 103)
  - F13 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 103, Folder 1)
- F13 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 104)
  - F13 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 104, Folder 1)
- F14 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 105)
  - F14 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 105, Folder 1)
- F14 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 106)
  - F14 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 106, Folder 1)
- F15 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 107)
  - F15 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 107, Folder 1)
- F15 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 108)
  - F15 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 108, Folder 1)
- F16 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 109)
  - F16 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 109, Folder 1)
- F16 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 110)
  - F16 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 110, Folder 1)
- F017 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 111)
  - F17 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 111, Folder 1)
- F17 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 112)
  - F17 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 112, Folder 1)
- F18 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 113)
  - F18 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 113, Folder 1)
- F18 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 114)
  - F18 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 114, Folder 1)
- F019 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 115)
  - F19 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 115, Folder 1)
- F19 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 116)
  - F19 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 116, Folder 1)
- F021 - Shop time and motion study. Text in film: 'hand assembly" (Box 117)
  - F21 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 117, Folder 1)
- F022 - Shop time and motion study. Text in film: 'cut out back lace' (Box 118)
  - F22 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 118, Folder 1)
- F023 - Shop time and motion study. August-April; Text in film: 'Flatlock, close, shoulder' (Box 119)
  - F23 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 119, Folder 1)
- F27 - Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop (Box 120)
  - F27 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 120, Folder 1)
- F28 - Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop (Box 121)
  - F28 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 121, Folder 1)
- F30 - Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop (Box 122)
  - F30 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 122, Folder 1)
- F31 - Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop (Box 123)
  - F31 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 123, Folder 1)
- F32 - Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop (Box 124)
  - F32 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 124, Folder 1)
- F33 - Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop (Box 125)
  - F33 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 125, Folder 1)
- F34 - Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop (Box 126)
  - F34 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 126, Folder 1)
- F39 - Shop time and motion study. Compares 2 factories, Taylor Style Efficiency (Box 127)
  - F39 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 127, Folder 1)
- F40 - Shop time and motion study. Woman ironing small pieces of cloth (Box 128)
  - F40 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 128, Folder 1)
- F041 - Shop time and motion study. Text in film: 'Stretch, work, and cut gadget (Box 129)
  - F41 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 129, Folder 1)
- F42 - Shop time and motion study. Film depicts lack of improvement in the Blossom Plastics (Box 130)
  - F42 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 130, Folder 1)
- F043 - Shop time and motion study. August 7; Text in film: 'Stitch Darts' (Box 131)
  - F43 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 131, Folder 1)
- F044 - Shop time and motion study. Text in film: 'Work simplification (Box 132)
  - F44 - Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 132, Folder 1)
- F55 - Union label commercials. Emma; Retired Worker (Box 133)
  - F55 - Union label commercials. Emma; Retired Worker (Box 133, Folder 1)
- F57 - Union label commercials. Emma; Retired Worker (Box 134)
  - F57 - Union label commercials. Emma; Retired Worker (Box 134, Folder 1)
- F57a - Union label commercials. 2 Commercials (Box 135)
  - F57a - Union label commercials. Emma; Retired Worker (Box 135, Folder 1)
- F58 - Union label commercials. 2 Commercials (Box 136)
  - F58 - Union label commercials. Emma; Retired Worker (Box 136, Folder 1)
- F58a - Union label commercials. Lillian (Box 137)
  - F58a- Union label commercials. Emma; Retired Worker (Box 137, Folder 1)
- F061 - Union labe commercials. 2 Commercials (Box 138)
  - F61 - Union label commercials. Emma; Retired Worker (Box 138, Folder 1)
- F75 - Sixth annual outing at Unity House (Box 139)
  - F75 - Sixth annual outing at Unity House (Box 139, Folder 1)
- F93 - Convention - Golden Jubilee, ILGWU, post event coverage (Box 140)
  - F93 - Convention - Golden Jubilee, ILGWU, post event coverage (Box 140, Folder 1)
- F135a - Union Health Center 50th Anniversary Celebration (Box 141)
  - F135a - Union Health Center 50th Anniversary Celebration (Box 141, Folder 1)
- F135b - Union Health Center 50th Anniversary Celebration (Box 142)
  - F135b - Union Health Center 50th Anniversary Celebration (Box 142, Folder 1)
- F135c - Union Health Center 50th Anniversary Celebration (Box 143)
  - F135c - Union Health Center 50th Anniversary Celebration (Box 143, Folder 1)
- F142 - Miscellaneous Rallies. Chorus and marching orchestra (Box 144)
  - F142 - Miscellaneous Rallies. Chorus and marching orchestra (Box 144, Folder 1)
- F143 - Miscellaneous Rallies. Chorus and marching orchestra (Box 145)
  - F143 - Miscellaneous Rallies. Chorus and marching orchestra (Box 145, Folder 1)
- V247 - Resolutions of the Convention. September 28, Support for ERA (Box 146)
  - V247 - Resolutions of the Convention. September 28, Support for ERA (Box 146, Folder 1)
- V248 - Continuation of Carter's speech. September 28; He defends legal right (Box 147)
  - V248 - Continuation of Carter's speech. September 28; He defends legal right (Box 147, Folder 1)
- We are one [Local 23-25 Chinatown Strike, 1982] (Box 148)
  - We are one [Local 23-25 Chinatown Strike, 1982] (Box 148, Folder 1)
- DVD copy of 16mm film in box 72b, 5780 AV; for part 2, see DVD in box 315, 5780 F; copy 1. (Box 149, Folder 1)
- DVD copy of 16mm film in box 72b, 5780 AV; for part 2, see DVD in box 315, 5780 F; copy 2. (Box 150, Folder 1)
- DVD copy of 16mm film in box 72b, 5780 AV; for part 2, see DVD in box 315, 5780 F; copy 3. (Box 151, Folder 1)
- ILGWU "European Labor Day" -- filmed by the ECA print #3 - 400 feet // 2 rolls of negative film -- WC/AR March; ILGWU March 1939-44 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  transferred from 16mm film
- Jay Mazur on McNeil Lehrer -- 8/20/1986 -- Homework (Box 152, Folder 2)
- ILGWU 'European Labor Day" filmed by the ECA print #3 - 400 ft. // 2 rolls of negative film: WC/AR March; ILGWU March 1939-44 (Box 152, Folder 3)
- Kheel Center, IlGWU -- Misc. rallies (Box 152, Folder 4)
  has a notation on the tape from 5780/73, may have been moved from that collection
- ILGWU Collection- Misc. rallies (Box 152, Folder 5)
  tape has a collection notation of 5780/73 - may have been moved from that collection
- ILGWU 1940 Convention (Box 152, Folder 6)
  1200 feet, transferred from 16mm film
- ILGWU 1940 Convention (Box 152, Folder 7)
  1200 feet - transferred from 16mm film
- ILGWU Anniversary - David Dubinsky (1957) - Print #4 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  1200 feet, transferred from 16 mm film
- ILGWU Anniversary - Dubinsky (1957) print #4 (Box 152, Folder 9)
- This is your life, Chick. -- Sheridan Elson -- 1986 (Box 152, Folder 10)
- Chaikin - Master Dub. Tyler narration (Box 152, Folder 11)
  this is a stereo tape
- City Club Luncheon -- 11/9/1984 -- Jay Mazur (Box 152, Folder 12)
- Jay Mazur Interview - Business Morning -- CNN-TV -- September 1, Monday, 6:30 AM (Box 152, Folder 13)
- Dressmakers Strike 1958 -- Part 1 of 2 (Box 153)
  - Dressmakers Strike 1958 -- Part 1 of 2 (Box 153, Folder 1)
- Dressmakers Strike 1958 -- Part 1 of 2 (Box 154)
  - Dressmakers Strike 1958 -- Part 1 of 2 (Box 154, Folder 1)
- Dressmakers Strike 1958 -- Part 1 of 2 (Box 155)
  - Dressmakers Strike 1958 -- Part 1 of 2 (Box 155, Folder 1)
- Dressmakers Strike 1958 -- Part 2 of 2 (Box 156)
  - Dressmakers Strike 1958 -- Part 1 of 2 (Box 156, Folder 1)
- Crafted With Pride: A Song for America's Textile Workers (Box 157, Folder 13)
  removed from box 81, which was deleted.
- With These Hands [made 9/29/2010] (Box 157, Folder 11)
- Part I Interview - Mr. Mrs. Vinson, G.C. Ginsburg (Box 157, Folder 1)
- The Eternal Light; NBC, June 29, 1958, Local 1783 IBEW, AFL-CIO (Box 157, Folder 2)
- Conference on the Draft-part #3; Stillman, J. McMurray, Woffard; John Stillman, Luncheon Meeting; Dr. Joseph P. McMurray, Harris Woffard (Box 157, Folder 3)
- Conference on the Draft - 11/11/1966 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  Part I - Tyler, Dr. Woll; Part #2 - Tyler, Col. Omer -- AVC Draft Conf., Plenary Session, Gus Tyler
- Chairman G.T. - #1; Col. Daniel Omer - #2 -- November 11 - 11:30 AM (Box 157, Folder 5)
- Conference on the Draft part I II - 11/18/1966 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  I - Tyler - Dr. Wool; II - Tyler - Col. Omer, Mr. Jones
- Sabbath Observance - Friday - 3:15-3:30 (Box 157, Folder 7)
- Unity House Archival (Box 157, Folder 8)
  MASTER
- Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire. Leon Stein Remembers (Box 157, Folder 9)
  V231
- We Are One (Chinese version) (Box 157, Folder 10)
- F93. ILGWU, Golden Jubilee Convention, 1950 (Box 158)
  - F93. ILGWU, Golden Jubilee Convention, 1950 (Box 158, Folder 1)
- "The Making of a Commercial" from the taping of the ILGWU third Chorus in Oct. 1979 (was to be part of the presentation for 1980 ILGWU convention NOW KILLED) -reel #2 (Box 159)
  - "The Making of a Commercial" from the taping of the ILGWU third Chorus in Oct. 1979 (was to be part of the presentation for 1980 ILGWU convention NOW KILLED) - 5 reels altogether. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    Paula Green Inc. Advertising, 500 Fifth Avenue, New York, New York 10036 Title: ILGWU/ILG 1160 (reel #30) Negatives Soundtrack -- reel #2
- "The Making of a Commercial" from the taping of the ILGWU third Chorus in Oct. 1979 (was to be part of the presentation for 1980 ILGWU convention NOW KILLED) - reel #3 #4 (Box 160)
  - "The Making of a Commercial" from the taping of the ILGWU third Chorus in Oct. 1979 (was to be part of the presentation for 1980 ILGWU convention NOW KILLED) - 5 reels altogether. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    Paula Green Inc. Advertising, 500 Fifth Avenue, New York, New York 10036 Title: ILGWU/ILG 1160 (reel #30) Negatives Soundtrack -- reel #3 #4
- "The Making of a Commercial" from the taping of the ILGWU third Chorus in Oct. 1979 (was to be part of the presentation for 1980 ILGWU convention NOW KILLED) - reel #1 amp; #5 (Box 161)
  - "The Making of a Commercial" from the taping of the ILGWU third Chorus in Oct. 1979 (was to be part of the presentation for 1980 ILGWU convention NOW KILLED) - 5 reels altogether. (Box 161, Folder 1)
    Paula Green Inc. Advertising, 500 Fifth Avenue, New York, New York 10036 Title: ILGWU/ILG 1160 (reel #30) Negatives Soundtrack -- reel #1 #5
- ILGWU "Making of a Commercial" Work pix out takes - see folder list for specifics (Box 162)
  - ILGWU/ILG 1160 (Reel #30) -- ILGWU "Making of a Commercial" Work pix out takes (Box 162, Folder 1)
    Paula Green Inc. Advertising, 500 Fifth Avenue, New York, New York 10036 -- reel label listing -- Instruments (2); unlabeled, loose rolls (9); Make-up, getting ready (2); Sound Booth (no sync)
- ILGWU "Making of a Commercial" Work pix out takes - see folder list for specifics (Box 163)
  - ILGWU/ILG 1160 (Reel #30) -- ILGWU "Making of a Commercial" (Box 163, Folder 1)
    Paula Green Inc. Advertising, 500 Fifth Avenue, New York, New York 10036 -- reel listing -- Paula Green talking to group; Sync Pix
- ILGWU "Making of a Commercial" Work pix out takes - see folder list for specifics (Box 164)
  - Title: ILGWU/ILG 1160 (Reel #30) - ILGWU "Making of a Commercial" (Box 164, Folder 1)
    Paula Green Inc. Advertising, 500 Fifth Avenue, New York, New York 10036 -- reel listing -- Video taping - Nat Eisenberg (2)
- ILGWU "Making of a Commercial" Work pix out takes - see folder list for specifics (Box 165)
  - Title: ILGWU/ILG 1160 (Reel #30) - ILGWU "Making of a Commercial" (Box 165, Folder 1)
    Paula Green Inc. Advertising, 500 Fifth Avenue, New York, New York 10036 -- reel listing -- Auditions; Conductor Singing
- ILGWU "Making of a Commercial" Work pix out takes - see folder list for specifics (Box 166)
  - Title: ILGWU/ILG 1160 (Reel #30) - ILGWU "Making of a Commercial" (Box 166, Folder 1)
- Union Label Commercials (Box 167)
  - Union Label Commercials [V65] (Box 167, Folder 1)
    Paula Green Advertising
- Union Label Commercials (Box 168)
  - Union Label Commercials - [V64] (Box 168, Folder 1)
- Film: COPE "Good Work for Democracy" (Box 169)
  - COPE "Good Work for Democracy" (Box 169, Folder 1)
- The Triangle Fire, by Leon Stein (Box 170, Folder 1)
  found in box 62 and moved
- The Triangle Fire, by Leon Stein (Box 171, Folder 1)
- #669 ILGWU "Desenfrenado" - Spanish - "Uncontrolled" -- 4/4/85, 1985 (Box 172, Folder 1)
- Chaikin - Tyler for Daniels -- 50 years with ILGWU (Box 173, Folder 1)
- Teper Memorial -- 5/21/81, 1981 (Box 174, Folder 1)
- Notes from the Fire - Chris Llewellyn - 1983 (Box 175, Folder 1)
- Labor Day 1984 (Box 176, Folder 1)
- June 13, 1985 - S.C. Chaikin - Ways + Means Committee (House) -- Re: Reagan Tax Reform Plan (Box 177, Folder 1)
- Labor Day -- 1984 (Box 178, Folder 1)
- Barry Farber -- WMCA -- 3/25/85, 1985 (Box 179, Folder 1)
- Pauline Newman Memorial -- 6/23/86, 1986 (Box 180, Folder 1)
- Pins + Needles - 1973 -- 25th Anniv. Edition (Box 181, Folder 1)
- Teper Memorial - 5/21/1985 (Box 182, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Motion Studies - Women Sewing -- this was copied for a researcher from material in box 2 -- see filemaker records (Box 183)
- ILGWU (Box 225, Folder 1)
- ILGWU (Box 226, Folder 1)
- ILGWU (Box 227, Folder 1)
- ILGWU (Box 228, Folder 1)
- Celia, Al/Al, Phyllis; Phyllis, Mac/Phil, Mac; Hope, Anna; Anna (Box 236, Folder 1)
  3 parts
- Celia, Al/Al, Phyllis; Phyllis, Mac/Phil, Mac; Hope, Anna; Anna (Box 237, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 248, Folder 1)
- David Dubinsky - #43 - Industrial Relations, Puerto Ricans (Box 259, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #1 (Box 266, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #2 - 5/30 (Box 267, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #3 - 5/30 (Box 268, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #1 - 6/2/86 (Box 269, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #2 - 6/2/86, 1986 (Box 270, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #3 - 6/2/86, 1986 (Box 271, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #1 - 6/2/86, 1986 (Box 272, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #2 - 6/2/86, 1986 (Box 273, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #1 - 6/3/86, 1986 (Box 274, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #2 - 6/3/86, 1986 (Box 275, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #3 - 6/3/86, 1986 (Box 276, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #1 - 6/3/86, 1986 (Box 277, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #2 - 6/3/86, 1986 (Box 278, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #1 - 6/4/86, 1986 (Box 279, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #2 - 6/4/86, 1986 (Box 280, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #3 - 6/4/86, 1986 (Box 281, Folder 1)
- ILGWU 6/4/86, 1986 (Box 282, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #2 - 6/4/86, 1986 (Box 283, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #3 - 6/4/86, 1986 (Box 284, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #1 - 6/5/86, 1986 (Box 285, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #2 - 6/5/86, 1986 (Box 286, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #1 - 6/5/86, 1986 (Box 287, Folder 1)